A Guide to the Richmond YWCA Archives 1893-1980
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Series VI- Case Studies
  - Barnes, Emily (Box-folder 46:44)
  - Barnes, Marian (Box-folder 46:45)
  - Barnett, Elizabeth (Box-folder 46:46)
  - Barnwiski-Thier, Helen (Box-folder 46:47)
  - Barton, Violet (Box-folder 46:48)
  - Baskerville, Alice (Box-folder 46:49)
  - Bateman, Corinne Mae (Box-folder 46:50)
  - Baxandall, Ann (Box-folder 46:51)
  - Baxter, Margaret (Box-folder 46:52)
  - Baylor, Margaret (Box-folder 46:53)
  - Beasley, Florence (Box-folder 46:54)
  - Beazley, Ann (Box-folder 46:55)
  - Beazley, Edith (Box-folder 46:56)
  - Beazley, Emma (Box-folder 46:57)
  - Becker, Edna (Box-folder 46:58)
  - Bell, Virginia Louise (Box-folder 46:59)
  - Bernstien, Stiffie (Box-folder 46:60)
  - Black, Gertrude (Box-folder 46:61)
  - Blackburn, Annie (Box-folder 46:62)
  - Blackburn, Doris (Box-folder 46:63)
  - Bloxton, Estelle (Box-folder 46:64)
  - Bohannon, Patsy (Box-folder 46:65)
  - Bohen, Cora Mae (Box-folder 46:66)
  - Bond, Dorothy (Box-folder 46:67)
  - Bordley, Gayle (Box-folder 46:68)
  - Bowen, Geraldine (Box-folder 46:69)
  - Bowles, Virginia (Box-folder 46:70)
  - Bowman, Jane (Box-folder 46:71)
  - Boyd, Celia (Box-folder 46:72)
  - Branch, Ann (Box-folder 46:73)
  - Bratton, Edith (Box-folder 46:74)
  - Braxton, Mary Frances (Box-folder 46:75)
  - Breon, John and Mary (Box-folder 46:76)
  - Britton, Bertha and Norma (Box-folder 46:77)
  - Brizendine, Earnestine (Box-folder 46:78)
  - Broach, Virginia (Box-folder 46:79)
  - Brooking, Barabara (Box-folder 46:80)
  - Brooks, Lois (Box-folder 46:81)
  - Brooks, Mary (Box-folder 46:82)
  - Brown, Daisey (Box-folder 46:83)
  - Brown, Elizabeth (Box-folder 46:84)
  - Brown, Laverne (Box-folder 46:85)
  - Brown, Wilson (Box-folder 46:86)
  - Bruant, Hazel (Box-folder 46:87)
  - Bruce, Jean (Box-folder 46:88)
  - Bruner, Benjamin (Box-folder 46:89)
  - Brunson, Charity (Box-folder 46:90)
  - Bryan, Mrs. M. (Box-folder 46:91)
  - Bryant, Beatrice (Box-folder 46:92)
  - Bryson, Anna Lou (Box-folder 46:93)
  - Bubank, Claudine (Box-folder 46:94)
  - Bubank, Doris (Box-folder 47:1)
  - Bubank, Doris Mae (Box-folder 47:2)
  - Bullock, Lillian Bell (Box-folder 47:3)
  - Bunce, Betty Lou (Box-folder 47:4)
  - Burch, Helen (Box-folder 47:5)
  - Burch, Mildred (Box-folder 47:6)
  - Burgess, Frances (Box-folder 47:7)
  - Burton, Mary (Box-folder 47:8)
  - Burton, Virginia (Box-folder 47:9)
  - Butler, Alice (Box-folder 47:10)
  - Butler, Mabel (Box-folder 47:11)
  - Caloway, Rachel (Box-folder 47:12)
  - Camp, Anna (Box-folder 47:13)
  - Campbell, Carrie (Box-folder 47:14)
  - Campbell, Ellie (Box-folder 47:15)
  - Campbell, Mary Elizabeth (Box-folder 47:16)
  - Carman, Ruby (Box-folder 47:17)
  - Carneal, Barbara (Box-folder 47:18)
  - Carr, Marguerite (Box-folder 47:19)
  - Carter, Julie (Box-folder 47:20)
  - Carter, Lorraine (Box-folder 47:21)
  - Carter, Marie (Box-folder 47:22)
  - Carter, Naeleene (Box-folder 47:23)
  - Case, Viola (Box-folder 47:24)
  - Castaing, Elizabeth (Box-folder 47:25)
  - Catlett, Rosalie (Box-folder 47:26)
  - Chalkley, Irma (Box-folder 47:27)
  - Chalkley, Sarah (Box-folder 47:28)
  - Chancellor, Lucille (Box-folder 47:29)
  - Childress, Lucile (Box-folder 47:30)
  - Chockley, Virginia (Box-folder 47:31)
  - Christopher, Nancy (Box-folder 47:32)
  - Ciparani, Patsy (Box-folder 47:33)
  - Clark, Edith Mae (Box-folder 47:34)
  - Clark, Gladys (Box-folder 47:35)
  - Clark, Louise (Box-folder 47:36)
  - Cobb, Elsie (Box-folder 47:37)
  - Cobbs, Catherine (Box-folder 47:38)
  - Cochrane, Marie (Box-folder 47:39)
  - Cole, Yvonne (Box-folder 47:40)
  - Coleman, Judith (Box-folder 47:41)
  - Coleman, Martha (Box-folder 47:42)
  - Colquitt, Blanche (Box-folder 47:43)
  - Conn, Ruth (Box-folder 47:44)
  - Connell, Mary Ellen (Box-folder 47:45)
  - Cope, Dorothy (Box-folder 47:46)
  - Coppage, Phoebe (Box-folder 47:47)
  - Corling, Blanche (Box-folder 47:48)
  - Cosby, Page, Lucile, Helen (Box-folder 47:49)
  - Cosner, Elsie (Box-folder 47:50)
  - Coulton, Maude (Box-folder 47:51)
  - Cousins, Lois (Box-folder 47:52)
  - Cowan, Laveta (Box-folder 47:53)
  - Craddock, Mary Taylor (Box-folder 47:54)
  - Craft, Catherine (Box-folder 47:55)
  - Cramer, Elizabeth (Box-folder 47:56)
  - Craxton, Mabel (Box-folder 47:57)
  - Breasy, Margaret (Box-folder 47:58)
  - Cress, Lois (Box-folder 47:59)
  - Cregger, Bettie (Box-folder 47:60)
  - Crigger, Ella (Box-folder 47:61)
  - Crosswhite, Margaret (Box-folder 47:62)
  - Culley, Rebecca (Box-folder 47:63)
  - Cummings, Ingrid (Box-folder 47:64)
  - Cunningham, Peggy (Box-folder 47:65)
  - Curry, Jean (Box-folder 47:66)
  - Dandridge, Mary (Box-folder 47:67)
  - Daniels, Mavournnen (Box-folder 47:68)
  - Danner, Mildred (Box-folder 47:69)
  - Davis, Charlotte (Box-folder 47:70)
  - Davis, Pauline (Box-folder 47:71)
  - Davis, Veronica (Box-folder 47:72)
  - Davole, Pauline (Box-folder 47:73)
  - Deal, Dorris (Box-folder 47:74)
  - Dean, Audrey (Box-folder 47:75)
  - Decker, Kay (Box-folder 47:76)
  - Demsy, Margaret (Box-folder 48:1)
  - Derr, Elsie (Box-folder 48:2)
  - Dicken, Marion (Box-folder 48:3)
  - Dix, Mabel (Box-folder 48:4)
  - Dixon, Mrs. B. (Box-folder 48:5)
  - Doane, June (Box-folder 48:6)
  - Dobbs, Helen (Box-folder 48:7)
  - Dogget, Virginia (Box-folder 48:8)
  - Dolan, Margaret (Box-folder 48:10)
  - Dolan, Mary (Box-folder 48:11)
  - Donald, E.M. (Box-folder 48:12)
  - Douglas, Margaret (Box-folder 48:13)
  - Dowdy, Bessie (Box-folder 48:14)
  - Dowdy, Sylvia (Box-folder 48:15)
  - Drake, Lurline (Box-folder 48:16)
  - Drew, Doris (Box-folder 48:17)
  - Dudley, Elise (Box-folder 48:18)
  - Duncan, Evelyn (Box-folder 48:19)
  - Dunkum, Ruby (Box-folder 48:20)
  - Dunn, Beatrice (Box-folder 48:21)
  - Dunnavant, Betty (Box-folder 48:22)
  - Dupre, Josie (Box-folder 48:23)
  - Durette, Daisy (Box-folder 48:24)
  - Eagle, Martha (Box-folder 48:25)
  - Eaton, Alice (Box-folder 48:26)
  - Eckert, Mildred (Box-folder 48:27)
  - Edgar, Alberta (Box-folder 48:28)
  - Edwards, Nora (Box-folder 48:29)
  - Eggleston, June (Box-folder 48:30)
  - Elizabeth, Frances (Box-folder 48:31)
  - Elliot, Carolyn (Box-folder 48:32)
  - Ellis, Loyd (Box-folder 48:33)
  - Ellwood, Mary (Box-folder 48:34)
  - Ely, Peggy (Box-folder 48:35)
  - Emory, Alice (Box-folder 48:36)
  - English, Naomi (Box-folder 48:37)
  - Enroughy, Elizabeth (Box-folder 48:38)
  - Eubank, Mary (Box-folder 48:39)
  - Evans, Esther (Box-folder 48:40)
  - Evans, Fay (Box-folder 48:41)
  - Evand, Winston (Box-folder 48:42)
  - Everett, Mamie (Box-folder 48:43)
  - Farley, Dutch (Box-folder 48:44)
  - Faust, Geneva (Box-folder 48:45)
  - Fawcitt, Ruth (Box-folder 48:46)
  - Figg, Robert (Box-folder 48:47)
  - Filie, Mary (Box-folder 48:48)
  - Fink, Shirley (Box-folder 48:49)
  - Fisher, Colleen (Box-folder 48:50)
  - Fleming, Lois (Box-folder 48:51)
  - Floyd, Sandra (Box-folder 48:52)
  - Foley, Violet (Box-folder 48:53)
  - Foster, Margaret (Box-folder 48:54)
  - Fountain, Marie (Box-folder 48:55)
  - Franck, Arline (Box-folder 48:56)
  - Franklin, Betty (Box-folder 48:57)
  - Franklin, Doris (Box-folder 48:58)
  - Frazier, Gertrude (Box-folder 48:59)
  - Fuggett, Pauline (Box-folder 48:60)
  - Gaines, Alma (Box-folder 48:61)
  - Gallimore, Margaret (Box-folder 48:62)
  - Ganderson, Robinette (Box-folder 48:63)
  - Ganzert, Margaret (Box-folder 48:64)
  - Garnett, Betty (Box-folder 48:65)
  - Garnett, Lois (Box-folder 48:66)
  - Garnett, Margaret (Box-folder 48:67)
  - Garrett, Vodivee (Box-folder 48:68)
  - Garth, Lucile (Box-folder 48:69)
  - Gary, Evelyn (Box-folder 48:70)
  - Gary, Florine (Box-folder 48:71)
  - Gayle, Ada (Box-folder 48:72)
  - Geaweald, Karen (Box-folder 48:73)
  - Geissinger, Emma (Box-folder 48:74)
  - George, Eloise (Box-folder 48:75)
  - George, Margaret (Box-folder 48:76)
  - Gerhardt, Lillian (Box-folder 48:77)
  - Gholson, Annie (Box-folder 48:78)
  - Gibson, Elise (Box-folder 48:79)
  - Gibson, Hylda (Box-folder 48:80)
  - Gilliam, France and Edwin (Box-folder 48:81)
  - Gladys, Sudie and Pearl (Box-folder 48:82)
  - Glazebrook, Grace (Box-folder 48:83)
  - Glidewell, Paul (Box-folder 48:84)
  - Glover, Eileen (Box-folder 48:85)
  - Godsey, Carol (Box-folder 48:86)
  - Godsey, Ethel and James (Box-folder 48:87)
  - Godsey, Lysle (Box-folder 48:88)
  - Goodwin, Mattie (Box-folder 49:1)
  - Goswick, Eunice (Box-folder 49:2)
  - Glover, Anita (Box-folder 49:3)
  - Grace, Barbara (Box-folder 49:4)
  - Granderson, Robnette (Box-folder 49:5)
  - Gray, Dorothy (Box-folder 49:6)
  - Gray, Eloise (Box-folder 49:7)
  - Gray, Shirley (Box-folder 49:8)
  - Greaver, Lucy (Box-folder 49:9)
  - Green, Alice (Box-folder 49:10)
  - Green, Ruth (Box-folder 49:11)
  - Greenwood, Marjorie (Box-folder 49:12)
  - Gregory, Catherine (Box-folder 49:13)
  - Gregory, Laura (Box-folder 49:14)
  - Griffith, Patsy (Box-folder 49:15)
  - Grove, Bessie (Box-folder 49:16)
  - Grubbs, Dorothy (Box-folder 49:17)
  - Guild, Barbara (Box-folder 49:18)
  - Guiles, Edith (Box-folder 49:18)
  - Gulley, Dorothy (Box-folder 49:19)
  - Gunzburg, Hilda (Box-folder 49:20)
  - Guy, Mary (Box-folder 49:21)
  - Hackett, Helen (Box-folder 49:22)
  - Hager, Alda (Box-folder 49:23)
  - Hager, Alda (Box-folder 49:24)
  - Hairfield, Vernelle (Box-folder 49:25)
  - Hall, Alice (Box-folder 49:26)
  - Hall, Clyde (Box-folder 49:27)
  - Hall, Earnie (Box-folder 49:28)
  - Hall, Irene (Box-folder 49:29)
  - Hall, Martha (Box-folder 49:30)
  - Hankins, Sara (Box-folder 49:31)
  - Hann, Phyllis (Box-folder 49:32)
  - Hardee, Gaynelle (Box-folder 49:33)
  - Harding, Jennie (Box-folder 49:34)
  - Hardy, Marguerite (Box-folder 49:35)
  - Harler, Edith (Box-folder 49:36)
  - Harler, Roger (Box-folder 49:37)
  - Harlow, Inez (Box-folder 49:38)
  - Harrell, Ella (Box-folder 49:39)
  - Harris, Anne (Box-folder 49:40)
  - Harris, Betty (Box-folder 49:41)
  - Harris, Dorothy (Box-folder 49:42)
  - Harris, Nova (Box-folder 49:43)
  - Hartman, Betsy (Box-folder 49:44)
  - Hartman, Marian (Box-folder 49:45)
  - Harvey, Lucius (Box-folder 49:46)
  - Hatcher, Jewel (Box-folder 49:47)
  - Haw, Joyce (Box-folder 49:48)
  - Hazard, Robinette (Box-folder 49:49)
  - Heath, Evelyn (Box-folder 49:50)
  - Heath, Louise (Box-folder 49:51)
  - Hedge, Myrtle (Box-folder 49:52)
  - Heland, Redford (Box-folder 49:53)
  - Helmick, Frances (Box-folder 49:54)
  - Hicks, Lavonia (Box-folder 49:55)
  - Hicks, Mary (Box-folder 49:56)
  - Hill, Betty (Box-folder 49:57)
  - Hill, Edith (Box-folder 49:58)
  - Hill, Ruby (Box-folder 49:59)
  - Hipp, Floyd (Box-folder 49:60)
  - Hobson, Alice (Box-folder 49:61)
  - Hodges, Peggy (Box-folder 49:62)
  - Hoeny, Isabel (Box-folder 49:63)
  - Holman, Louise (Box-folder 49:64)
  - Holt, Jeanette (Box-folder 49:65)
  - Holt, Marjorie (Box-folder 49:66)
  - Holt, Pearl (Box-folder 49:67)
  - Hotz, Mary (Box-folder 49:68)
  - Howell, Ruth (Box-folder 49:69)
  - Howle, Alice and Paul (Box-folder 49:70)
  - Hudson, Ola (Box-folder 49:71)
  - Hughes, Mae (Box-folder 49:72)
  - Hughes, Maude and Josephine (Box-folder 49:73)
  - Hunt, Alice (Box-folder 49:74)
  - Hunter, Dorothy (Box-folder 49:75)
  - Hyatt, Annie (Box-folder 49:76)
  - Hyman, Estelle (Box-folder 49:77)
  - Inge, Evelyn (Box-folder 49:78)
  - Irving, John (Box-folder 49:79)
  - James, Catherine (Box-folder 49:80)
  - James, Lillie (Box-folder 49:81)
  - Jaralls, Doris (Box-folder 49:82)
  - Jarvis, Joyce (Box-folder 49:83)
  - Jasper, Mary (Box-folder 49:84)
  - Jasper, Vivian (Box-folder 50:1)
  - Jefferson, Thelma (Box-folder 50:2)
  - Jennings, Virginia (Box-folder 50:3)
  - Jeter, Frances (Box-folder 50:4)
  - Johnson, Bernice (Box-folder 50:5)
  - Johnson, Carolyn (Box-folder 50:6)
  - Johnson, Lois (Box-folder 50:7)
  - Johnson, Lucile (Box-folder 50:8)
  - Johnson, Priscilla (Box-folder 50:9)
  - Johnson, Sarah (Box-folder 50:10)
  - Jolly, Alice (Box-folder 50:11)
  - Jones, Betty (Box-folder 50:12)
  - Jones, E.M. (Box-folder 50:13)
  - Jones, Margaret (Box-folder 50:14)
  - Jones, Mildred (Box-folder 50:15)
  - Jones, Oliva (Box-folder 50:16)
  - Jones, Thelma (Box-folder 50:17)
  - Joyner, Frances (Box-folder 50:18)
  - Karnes, Emma (Box-folder 50:19)
  - Kay, Helen (Box-folder 50:20)
  - Kelly, Dorothy (Box-folder 50:21)
  - Kelly, Emma (Box-folder 50:22)
  - Kendall, Barbara (Box-folder 50:23)
  - Kerestis, Edith (Box-folder 50:24)
  - Key, Pearl (Box-folder 50:25)
  - Kidd, Patsy (Box-folder 50:26)
  - Kidd, Rita (Box-folder 50:27)
  - Kidd, Virginia (Box-folder 50:28)
  - Kilburn, Iris (Box-folder 50:29)
  - King, Josephine (Box-folder 50:30)
  - King, Mabel (Box-folder 50:31)
  - Krtley, Gertrude (Box-folder 50:32)
  - Kitchen, Evelyn (Box-folder 50:33)
  - Krakow, Edward (Box-folder 50:34)
  - Lawrence, Esther (Box-folder 50:35)
  - Lawson, Dorcas (Box-folder 50:36)
  - Layne, Doris (Box-folder 50:37)
  - Leake, Katherine (Box-folder 50:38)
  - Ledbetter, Phyllis (Box-folder 50:39)
  - Lee, Gertrude (Box-folder 50:40)
  - Lee, Lillian (Box-folder 50:41)
  - Lee, Mildred (Box-folder 50:42)
  - Leftwich, Dorothy (Box-folder 50:43)
  - Lehmen, Annie (Box-folder 50:44)
  - Lenker, Velma (Box-folder 50:45)
  - Leonard, Margaret (Box-folder 50:46)
  - Lewis, Darkes (Box-folder 50:47)
  - Lewis, Vivian (Box-folder 50:48)
  - Lighter, Pauline (Box-folder 50:49)
  - Linder, Juliana (Box-folder 50:50)
  - Lipscomb, Richard (Box-folder 50:51)
  - Lipscomb, Elsa (Box-folder 50:52)
  - Litchfield, Dorothy (Box-folder 50:53)
  - Little, Ruth (Box-folder 50:54)
  - Llewellyn, Donnie (Box-folder 50:55)
  - Lockett, Annie (Box-folder 50:56)
  - Lockhardt, Jane (Box-folder 50:57)
  - Longhead, Day (Box-folder 50:58)
  - Loving, Pearl (Box-folder 50:59)
  - Lowery, Pearl (Box-folder 50:60)
  - Lownie, Audrey (Box-folder 50:61)
  - Luda, Virginia (Box-folder 50:62)
  - Martin, Dorothy (Box-folder 50:63)
  - Marshall, Mary (Box-folder 50:64)
  - Marshall, Mrs, E.A. (Box-folder 50:65)
  - Martin, Alma (Box-folder 50:66)
  - Martin, Ethelyn (Box-folder 50:67)
  - Martin, Florence (Box-folder 50:68)
  - Martin, Frances (Box-folder 50:69)
  - Martin, Maevernon (Box-folder 50:70)
  - Martin, Margaret (Box-folder 50:71)
  - Martin, Terry (Box-folder 50:72)
  - Mason, Anna (Box-folder 50:73)
  - Mason, Frances (Box-folder 50:74)
  - Mason, Mary (Box-folder 50:75)
  - Massey, Louise (Box-folder 50:76)
  - Matthews, Orville (Box-folder 50:77)
  - Mauck, Priscilla (Box-folder 50:78)
  - Max, Louise (Box-folder 50:79)
  - McClaren, Lucile (Box-folder 50:80)
  - McCoy, Leona (Box-folder 50:81)
  - McCoy, Marie (Box-folder 50:82)
  - McDaniel, Marie (Box-folder 50:83)
  - McDonaldson, Sallie (Box-folder 50:84)
  - McFall, Dorothy (Box-folder 50:85)
  - McFeeders, Lucy (Box-folder 50:86)
  - McGregor, Hilary (Box-folder 50:87)
  - Julia, McIntire (Box-folder 50:88)
  - McQuay, Marion (Box-folder 50:89)
  - Mecale, Hilda (Box-folder 50:90)
  - Meeks, Margaret (Box-folder 50:91)
  - Meyers, Joseph (Box-folder 50:92)
  - Middleton, Mary (Box-folder 51:1)
  - Middleton, Clara (Box-folder 51:2)
  - Miller, Virginia (Box-folder 51:3)
  - Mills, Mabel (Box-folder 51:4)
  - Mills, Shirley (Box-folder 51:5)
  - Pearl, Minton (Box-folder 51:6)
  - Moeller, Virginia (Box-folder 51:7)
  - Monterio, Fannie (Box-folder 51:8)
  - Montgomery, Jo Ann (Box-folder 51:9)
  - Montgomery, Lorena (Box-folder 51:10)
  - Moore, Edna (Box-folder 51:11)
  - Moore, Hester (Box-folder 51:12)
  - Moore, Nancy (Box-folder 51:13)
  - Moore, Virginia (Box-folder 51:14)
  - Morris, Helen (Box-folder 51:15)
  - Mountford, Lelia (Box-folder 51:16)
  - Moutz, Oleana (Box-folder 51:17)
  - Murphy, Margaret (Box-folder 51:18)
  - Myers, Evelyn (Box-folder 51:19)
  - Napier, Connie (Box-folder 51:20)
  - Napier, Patsy (Box-folder 51:21)
  - Nash, Sadie (Box-folder 51:22)
  - Nearhood, Anna (Box-folder 51:23)
  - Neighley, Evelyn (Box-folder 51:24)
  - Neustadt, Charity (Box-folder 51:25)
  - Newall, Lois (Box-folder 51:26)
  - Niedermyer, Ruby (Box-folder 51:27)
  - Noel, Mary (Box-folder 51:28)
  - Notham, Gerda (Box-folder 51:29)
  - Nunally, Margarette (Box-folder 51:30)
  - O'Dell, Lois (Box-folder 51:31)
  - Oliver, Mary (Box-folder 51:32)
  - Oliver, Myrtle (Box-folder 51:33)
  - Orebough, Jane (Box-folder 51:34)
  - Osborne, Adelaide (Box-folder 51:35)
  - Osborne, Louise (Box-folder 51:36)
  - Ossman, Anne (Box-folder 51:37)
  - Ottolengui, Rosalie (Box-folder 51:38)
  - Outland, Mary (Box-folder 51:39)
  - Overby, Sarah (Box-folder 51:40)
  - Overstreet, Laura (Box-folder 51:41)
  - Owen, Edith (Box-folder 51:42)
  - Owen, Jewel (Box-folder 51:43)
  - Oyer, Alice (Box-folder 51:44)
  - Pace, Linda (Box-folder 51:45)
  - Packett, Alma (Box-folder 51:46)
  - Pallinder, Louise (Box-folder 51:57)
  - Palmer, Edna (Box-folder 51:58)
  - Pamwell, Elinor (Box-folder 51:59)
  - Parente, Mary (Box-folder 51:60)
  - Parker, Barbara (Box-folder 51:61)
  - Parker, Margaret (Box-folder 51:62)
  - Parrish, Pearle (Box-folder 51:63)
  - Parsons, Margaret (Box-folder 51:64)
  - Patrick, Brenda (Box-folder 51:65)
  - Patrick, Emma (Box-folder 51:66)
  - Patterson, Carrie (Box-folder 51:67)
  - Patton, Elizabeth (Box-folder 51:68)
  - Payne, Virginia (Box-folder 51:69)
  - Pearce, Margaret (Box-folder 51:70)
  - Pearson, Virginia (Box-folder 51:71)
  - Pender, Hazel (Box-folder 51:72)
  - Pendleton, Edna (Box-folder 51:73)
  - Pennington, Ruth (Box-folder 51:74)
  - Perdue, Elise (Box-folder 51:75)
  - Perkins, Mary (Box-folder 51:76)
  - Perr, H.E. (Box-folder 51:77)
  - Perry, Alice (Box-folder 51:78)
  - Peters, Sylvia (Box-folder 51:79)
  - Petersiel, Pearl (Box-folder 51:80)
  - Petit, Margaret (Box-folder 51:81)
  - Philman, Sue (Box-folder 51:82)
  - Pierce, Bernice (Box-folder 51:83)
  - Pitchford, Mary (Box-folder 51:84)
  - Planz, Sadie (Box-folder 51:85)
  - Pleasants, Margaret (Box-folder 51:86)
  - Pond, Gertrude (Box-folder 51:87)
  - Ponton, Theresa (Box-folder 51:88)
  - Poole, Laura (Box-folder 51:89)
  - Poppas, Madelene (Box-folder 51:90)
  - Portis, Elizabeth (Box-folder 51:91)
  - Powell, Daisy (Box-folder 51:92)
  - Powell, Mae Belle (Box-folder 51:93)
  - Powell, Nellie (Box-folder 51:94)
  - Powers, Carol (Box-folder 51:95)
  - Pruitt, Leuter (Box-folder 51:96)
  - Purnell, Arthur (Box-folder 51:97)
  - Pusey, Imogene (Box-folder 51:98)
  - Putze, Phyllis (Box-folder 51:99)
  - Radvany, Elsie (Box-folder 51:100)
  - Ragland, Evelyn (Box-folder 51:101)
  - Raikes, Margaret and Edward (Box-folder 51:102)
  - Rainey, Barbara (Box-folder 51:103)
  - Raleigh, Eleanor (Box-folder 51:104)
  - Ralston, Mary and Josephine (Box-folder 51:105)
  - Ramey, Clara (Box-folder 51:106)
  - Ransome, Janie (Box-folder 51:107)
  - Rasnick, Helen (Box-folder 51:108)
  - Rawlings, Marian (Box-folder 52:1)
  - Rawlins, Daphine (Box-folder 52:2)
  - Redden, Mary (Box-folder 52:3)
  - Redick, Bessie (Box-folder 52:4)
  - Reese, Sandra (Box-folder 52:5)
  - Revere, Elizabeth (Box-folder 52:6)
  - Rhoten, Frances (Box-folder 52:7)
  - Rice, Helen (Box-folder 52:8)
  - Richardson, Dorothy (Box-folder 52:9)
  - Richmond, Mary (Box-folder 52:10)
  - Richmond, Virgie (Box-folder 52:11)
  - Riddle, Charles (Box-folder 52:12)
  - Rider, Helen (Box-folder 52:13)
  - Riggs, Sharon (Box-folder 52:14)
  - Rivers, Joyce (Box-folder 52:15)
  - Roach, Lillian (Box-folder 52:15)
  - Roach, Margaret (Box-folder 52:16)
  - Roane, Dorothy (Box-folder 52:17)
  - Roanes, Gladys (Box-folder 52:18)
  - Robertson, Catherine (Box-folder 52:19)
  - Robertson, Lucile (Box-folder 52:20)
  - Rochelle, Etheridge (Box-folder 52:21)
  - Rogers, Louise and Rebecca (Box-folder 52:22)
  - Ropester, Alice (Box-folder 52:23)
  - Ross, Delores (Box-folder 52:24)
  - Rowdey, Phyllis (Box-folder 52:25)
  - Ruff, Delores (Box-folder 52:26)
  - Rupp, Veronica (Box-folder 52:27)
  - Rush, Roaslie (Box-folder 52:28)
  - Russell, Sarah (Box-folder 52:29)
  - Russell, Violet (Box-folder 52:30)
  - Rynoldo, Dorcos (Box-folder 52:31)
  - Saag, Aino (Box-folder 52:32)
  - Sabean, Jean (Box-folder 52:33)
  - Sabol, Agnes (Box-folder 52:34)
  - Sadie, Greene (Box-folder 52:35)
  - Salisbury, Helen (Box-folder 52:36)
  - Sandridge, Frances (Box-folder 52:37)
  - Saunders, Dorothy (Box-folder 52:38)
  - Saunders, Ruth (Box-folder 52:39)
  - Savage, Olivia (Box-folder 52:40)
  - Schoffner, Catherine (Box-folder 52:41)
  - Schmidt, Margaret (Box-folder 52:42)
  - Schulthrope, Rosebud (Box-folder 52:43)
  - Schwartz, Helen (Box-folder 52:44)
  - Scott, Jean (Box-folder 52:45)
  - Scott, Marian (Box-folder 52:46)
  - Scrogham, Mabel (Box-folder 52:47)
  - Seay, Audrey (Box-folder 52:48)
  - Seay, Bernice (Box-folder 52:49)
  - Seay, Madeline (Box-folder 52:50)
  - Seay, Mary (Box-folder 52:51)
  - Sechler, Dessie (Box-folder 52:52)
  - Selph, Belle (Box-folder 52:53)
  - Shackelford, Helen (Box-folder 52:53)
  - Sharpe, Ethel (Box-folder 52:54)
  - Shaw, Leslie (Box-folder 52:55)
  - Shaw, Margaret (Box-folder 52:56)
  - Sheets, Orna (Box-folder 52:57)
  - Sheffield, Violet (Box-folder 52:58)
  - Shields, Margaret (Box-folder 52:59)
  - Shipp, Joan (Box-folder 52:60)
  - Shirley, Oliver (Box-folder 52:61)
  - Silberman, Clara (Box-folder 52:62)
  - Simmons, Mary (Box-folder 52:63)
  - Simmons, Virginia (Box-folder 52:64)
  - Simmons, Pearl (Box-folder 52:65)
  - Skater, A.R. (Box-folder 52:66)
  - Sledd, Sarah (Box-folder 52:67)
  - Smith, Ellen (Box-folder 52:68)
  - Smith, Emily (Box-folder 52:69)
  - Smith, Gladys (Box-folder 52:70)
  - Smith, Grace (Box-folder 52:71)
  - Smith, Hilda (Box-folder 52:72)
  - Smith, Inez (Box-folder 52:73)
  - Smith, Jessie (Box-folder 52:74)
  - Smith, Lillian (Box-folder 52:75)
  - Smith, Marie (Box-folder 52:76)
  - Smith, Ruth (Box-folder 52:77)
  - Smithers, Katherine (Box-folder 52:78)
  - Snead, Daisy (Box-folder 52:79)
  - Snead, Eva (Box-folder 52:80)
  - Snead, I.V.B. (Box-folder 52:81)
  - Snead, Regina (Box-folder 52:82)
  - Snead, Vernelle (Box-folder 52:83)
  - Snelson, Grace (Box-folder 52:84)
  - Snoddy, Spain and Ida (Box-folder 52:85)
  - Spain, Rachel (Box-folder 52:86)
  - Speas, Lois (Box-folder 52:87)
  - Sprouse, Charlotte (Box-folder 53:1)
  - Stafford, Jean (Box-folder 53:2)
  - Staley, Elizabeth and Shirley (Box-folder 53:3)
  - Stanfield, Elizabeth (Box-folder 53:4)
  - Starbuck, Miriam (Box-folder 53:5)
  - Steiner, Sadye (Box-folder 53:6)
  - Stephenson, Janet (Box-folder 53:7)
  - Stern, Fannie (Box-folder 53:8)
  - Stevenson, Minnie (Box-folder 53:9)
  - Storch, Dorothy (Box-folder 53:10)
  - Stotesbury, Shirley (Box-folder 53:11)
  - Streever, Norma (Box-folder 53:12)
  - Strong, Dorothy (Box-folder 53:13)
  - Stump, Caroline (Box-folder 53:14)
  - Sullivan, Elizabeth (Box-folder 53:15)
  - Sullivan, Mamie (Box-folder 53:16)
  - Swank, Irene (Box-folder 53:17)
  - Swecker, Judy (Box-folder 53:18)
  - Talbot, Iola (Box-folder 53:19)
  - Taylor, Barbara (Box-folder 53:20)
  - Taylor, Blanche (Box-folder 53:21)
  - Taylor, Corine (Box-folder 53:22)
  - Taylor, Hannah (Box-folder 53:23)
  - Taylor, Inez (Box-folder 53:24)
  - Taylor, Mary (Box-folder 53:25)
  - Terrell, Ellen (Box-folder 53:26)
  - Terry, Ethel (Box-folder 53:27)
  - Thomas, Audry (Box-folder 53:28)
  - Thomas, Katherine (Box-folder 53:29)
  - Thomas, Pauline (Box-folder 53:30)
  - Thomas, Sylvia (Box-folder 53:31)
  - Thompson, Mary (Box-folder 53:32)
  - Tolley, Margaret (Box-folder 53:33)
  - Tomblin, Rebecca (Box-folder 53:34)
  - Tomes, Audrey (Box-folder 53:35)
  - Tomkins, Arlette (Box-folder 53:36)
  - Toone, Mabel (Box-folder 53:37)
  - Topien, Lillie (Box-folder 53:38)
  - Trent, Fannie (Box-folder 53:39)
  - Tripp, Alice (Box-folder 53:40)
  - Tuck, Lucy (Box-folder 53:41)
  - Tucker, Edith (Box-folder 53:42)
  - Twitchell, Amy (Box-folder 53:43)
  - Tyler, Dorothea (Box-folder 53:44)